desihits.com 2010-08-21

# Desi Radio, Videos and MP3s, Bollywood Hindi Songs, Bhangra Music and Podcasts at Desi Hits.com

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for DesiHits.com. While we will generally not share information that may be used to identify you, we do expect our policy statement will change as new ways to protect your confidentiality and new uses for information emerge. To that end, we value your comments about our privacy statement and invite you to e-mail us with suggestions and concerns. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy@DesiHits.com

**Information Collected**

When signing up for our services, you may be asked to provide information about you. All of the information is collected so that we can ensure that we can communicate with you when need be. Our privacy statement as set forth below is written so that you can understand exactly what we do and don’t do with your information.

Desi Hits! collects user submitted information such as name, email address and more, during registration for this site and use of many of its services. To view the full list of information collected during the registration please visit a registration page. Additional profile information may also be collected after registration. Collected information, among other uses, is used to allow listeners and others to search through the provided information (excluding email and password) to find relevant results.

Desi Hits! may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses may be recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

Collected email addresses are also used to send updates, newsletters or news regarding the service. You may choose not to receive this type of email by opting-out of future Desi Hits! modifications. All notification emails and newsletters will contain instructions for opting out of those communications in the future. Occasionally Desi Hits! may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain advertising partners from whom you have explicitly requested to receive information.

Note that if you sign up for service from one of our Partnership program affiliates, you hereby authorize us to share with the Partner the following information: e-mail address, name, title, entity, address and phone number (collectively “Contact Information”). No financial information will be shared. While we are not responsible for the acts of our partners, we encourage all of our Partners to adopt privacy policies that protect against the disclosure of personally identifiable parties to third persons.

**How Information Is Collected**

Registration and Account Set Up – When you sign up for services from Desi Hits! you will be asked to provide certain basic contact Information. After this is entered you, we will establish your account. You will be given the opportunity to provide additional Contact Information once your account is established. In addition, Financial Information may be collected to process payment for some of the premium services we provide or may provide in the future.

Customer Service – If you contact Desi Hits! either via e-mail, telephone or letter, we may keep a record of the correspondence.

Cookies – Desi Hits! may use cookies to store visitors preferences and to record session information to better the visitors experience and potentially better the advertising and marketing promotions relevance. Links – Desi Hits! is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the Desi Hits! website.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Collected Information**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Desi Hits! will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (2) to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Desi Hits! reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Desi Hits! or substantially it’s assets.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.
